Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-044
  - Reunion Homecoming (RH2000)-Service Alternative to Football-3/7 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Reunion Homecoming (RH2000)-Panels: State of Service at Stanford Today-4/7 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Reunion Homecoming (RH2000)-NAB pre-reception/main reception-5/7 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Reunion Homecoming (RH2000)-Alumni Outreach and Contact (mailings)-6/7 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Reunion Homecoming (RH2000)-General mtgs/Planning Materials w/index-7/7 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Homecoming-Committee mtgs, planning materials, publicity, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Homecoming-Committee mtgs, planning materials, publicity, 2002, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Charity Carnival-Fundraising, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Logistics, 1989-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Transportation, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Off Campus Fundraising, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Report, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Fundraising, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Logistics, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Entertainment, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Report, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Logistics, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Miscellany, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Campus Organization Letters, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Bus Transportation, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Community Carnival-Miscellany, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Community Carnival, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Community Day at Stanford-Student group grant applications, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Community Day at Stanford, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - John Gardner 80th Birthday, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - John Gardner Public Service Fellowship Ten Year Anniversary Event, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - John Gardner Public Service Fellowship Orientation Materials, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - John Gardner Fellowship at Community Foundation of Silicon Valley, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Francesca Gardner/John Gardner Book Event, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dulce Carothers-thank yous for Gardner booklet, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Gardner Symposium, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Haas Fellowships-Miscellany, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Haas Center Faculty Steering Committee, 1995, 1997, 1999, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Booklet-National Advisory Board Members, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Advisory Board (NAB) Materials, 1996, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - National Advisory Board Alumni Focus Group, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Citizen Leadership Development-Surdna Grant, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Multicultural Citizen Leadership-Surdna Grant (Part 3), 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Preliminary Report on Multicultural Citizenry SURDNA Project, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Mayfair Neighborhood Improvement Initiative, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Development Materials, circa 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Haas Strategic Planning Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - K-12 Task Group, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Haas Strategic Planning Materials, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Haas History/Background Material for Strategic Plan, 1983-2005 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Alternative Spring Break, 1999-2000, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Medical School-Public Service/Service-Learning (SMYSP, PriSMS), 1998-2001, 2003, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Haas Center History Project, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Youth Community Service-Program Evaluation Report, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Youth Community Service-Annual Reports, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Planning, early 1990s, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ten Year Anniversary Events, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Haas Coordinators, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Anthology for Youth (SAY), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - FIPSE Service Learning Portraiture Project, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Project DOSTI preparation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Casper Speeches (Haas bldg and SIW), 1993, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Building Dedication, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Haas Materials on Conflict Management, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Emergency Response, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Volunteers in Asia (VIA), 1989-2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Consulting Team (ACT), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Service-learning "pioneers" book event (Stanton, Giles, Cruz), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - National Advisory Board (NAB) Report 11/5/99, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Haas Evaluation materials, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - PDP/NAB/Campus Compact Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Volunteer Clearinghouse, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Upward Bound, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ravenswood Reads (1998-99 Report, etc.), circa 1996, 1998-1999, 2000, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Haas/Ravenswood City School District Partnerships, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ravenswood City School District Program Proposal, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Ravenswood Reads Report, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Ravenswood Reads-Report Winter 2002 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Ravenswood Tutors/Ravenswood Reads, 2003-2009 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Ravenswood Reads Tutoring Guide, circa 2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Faculty Service-Learning Institute (Marconi Center), 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Campus Compact Member Survey, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Campus Compact-membership, 1999, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - California Task Force 3 (CaTF-3)-Urban Search Rescue Volunteer Support Team, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - CaTF-3 Follow-ups, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Senate Presentation (Nadinne Cruz), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Staff Retreat Prep, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Staff Education, 1988, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Tim [Stanton-HCPS Director]-meetings, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Springboard, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Staff Retreat materials, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - National Advisory Board [NAB], 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Haas Center (incirca Cruz resignation and National Advisory Board materials), 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - FUSION-Social Entrepreneurship, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Stanford Leaders for Public Service, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Stanford Alliance for Service Through the Arts (SASTA), circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - STEPS (Stanford Exchange for Public Service) in D.C., 1988-2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes/Materials, 1995-1996, 1998, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Institute for Diversity in the Arts (IDA)-Irvine Arts Initiative, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - PSPCL (Public Service Program of Community Leadership) Publicity/Flyers, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - PSPCL (Public Service Program of Community Leadership) Communications, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - HUB (Haas Unifying Board), 1997, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Student Advisory Board (PSSAB), 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Stanford in Washington Director Search, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Visiting Mentors, 1994-1996, 1998-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Iranian/Iranian American public service opportunities, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Channel 51, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - General publicity, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Haas/Cowell HIV/AIDS programming, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Haas co-sponsorship/funding of student initiatives, 1995, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Clippings and News Releases, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Publicity/articles (copies), 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Young alumni outreach (including directories) "STARS", 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - School of Education and Haas Center, 1995, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Law School Outreach, 2000, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Graduate School of Business (GSB)-correspondence, 1999, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Stanford Alumni/Freshmen Interconnection Program (SA/FIP), 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Campaign for Undergraduate Education (CUE), 2000, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Job Descriptions, 1985, 1995, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Oakland Museum Internship, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Gardner Fellowship -"Celebrating a Decade", 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Civic Education Minor, 1996-1997, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Planning Group (internal), 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - VPSA Webmasters, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Haas Center Graduation Activities, 1998-2011 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Gardner Fellowship Dinner, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gardner Fellowship Correspondence, 1983-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Service-Learning Courses (grants, statistics, etc.), 1999-2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - East Palo Alto Seminar (POLS 198), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy Policy (Haas Ctr/SU), 1991-2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Haas Centennial Professorship, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fellowships-UPS, 2000-2004, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Walk the Talk Award, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Public Service Scholars Program (PSSP), 1990, 1991, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Public Service Inventory, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Upward Bound Grant (complete copy), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Upward Bound, 2000, 2001, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Public Service Research, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Stanford in Government, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Fellowship Evaluations (Gardner, Ford, Summer), 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - JGF (John Gardner Fellowship) Reunion Retreat Materials, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Haas Center Strategic Plan Binder, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Service Learning in Engineering, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Civic Engagement/Social Entrepreneurship, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Social Innovation Minor, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Guide to the Haas Center for Student Organizations, 2003-2004, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Community Service Work-Study, 1999-2006 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - VPUE general (incirca service-learning courses proposed and funded 98-99, 2001-07), 2003, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - School of Education (SUSE) and Haas Center, 2003, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Community-Based Research, 2003-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Steering Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - National Advisory Board, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Gardner Fellowship- Alumni Transition Task Force, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Leadership (development), 2003-2007 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Leadership Lecture Series-Development Materials, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Steering Committee Materials, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Stanford Writing Center/PWR, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - President Hennessy Meeting of August 2, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Community Health Working Group, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Medical School-Office of Community Health, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Roland Prize (inaugural), 2004 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Mission/Values Statement, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Outreach Plans, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Roland Prize 2005 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Opportunity Center/Don Barr, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Ortolano Board of Trustees Presentation, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Philanthropy Program Coordinator, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Philanthropy Working Group, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Vice Provost of Graduate Education(VPGE)-Graduate Students in Public Service, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Haas Publications-Miscellaneous (flyers, etc.), 2002, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - VIA (Volunteers in Asia)-including historical materials from '90s, 2000, 2002, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Haas Professor "Lecture on Public Service and the University", 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Gardner Fellowship EOY Evaluation/Orientation Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ford, Gardner Fellowships, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Public Service Leadership Fellows, 2001-2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Haas Summer Fellowships, 2002-2007 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Science in Service, 2003-2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Development/Outreach Strategy, 1999-2007, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Staff Organization Charts, 1999-2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Self-Study Materials, 2003-2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Advisory Board-Materials, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Steering Committee, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Partnership for Public Service, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public Service Scholars Program (PSSP), 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Upward Bound, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - College Access Transition Planning (Upward Bound Hiatus), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Environment-related public service opportunities, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Urban Studies Haas, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Roland Prize 2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Volunteer Operations Center Management Plan, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Call To Serve Initiative, 2004, 2006, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Vice Provost of Student Affairs(VPSA)-Sr. Leadership Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Center for Philanthropy and Civil Society (PACS), 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Stanford in Washington (SIW), 1986-1989, 2003, 2005, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gardner Fellowship/Stanford in Washington administrative transition, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Program, Policy, and Planning Team, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Interdepartmental Programs (IDPs), 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - National Advisory Board (NAB), 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Staff Meeting-Agendas/Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Staff Development, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - International Public Service, 2003, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Jumpstart, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - K-12 Education Initiative Campaign, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Roland Prize 2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Haas Courses (summer Fellowship Prep/Public Service Leadership), 2007 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Friends of Haas Dinner, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Conversations in Philanthropy (Book), 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - NAB (National Advisory Board), 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Executive Director Search, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Steering Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Haas Center Mural Project, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - John Gardner Public Service Fellowship information and application materials, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Roland Prize 2008 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Director - Haas Center (job description), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Friends of Haas Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Visiting Practitioner (Dan Karslake), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - NAB (National Advisory Board), 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - John Gardner Fellowship Association Retreat ("Alumni Facebook"), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Stanford Service-Learning Faculty Institute-Course Reader, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Faculty Steering Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board), 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - New Staff Information, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Roland Prize, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Inclusive Haas Steering Committee, 2008-2011 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 25th Anniversary Celebration, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Roland Prize, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Staff Meetings 04/09-08/09, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - All-Staff Meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Senior Leadership Team (SLT) Meetings 4/14/09-9/09/09, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Senior Leadership Team (SLT) Meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - PSSAB (Public Service Student Advisory Board)-Packet Materials, etc., 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Meeting Agendas, etcirca, 2009-2012 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Senior Leadership Team (SLT) Meetings, 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - All-Staff Meetings, 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Haas Evaluation RFP (design and plan), 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Senior Leadership Meetings, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - All-Staff Meetings, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Leadership Initiative (SLI)-Campus Compact grant, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - National Advisory Board [NAB] bios-new members, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - All-Staff Meetings, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Senior Leadership Team (SLT) Meetings, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - All-Staff Meetings, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Inter-Departmental Meetings, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student-led Affiliates, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Corporate Social Responsibility Fellowship-concept paper, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 17)